

AKSHAF MULLA



+971504243914



akshafmulla@gmail.com



46 Alhamriya Building, Room No. 301, Behind Umm AlnQuwain Bank, Khalid Bin Waleed Street, Bur Dubai.

SOCIALS

linkedin.com/in/akshafmulla-65100a21/

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, Angular, Backbase
- Javascript, Typescript
- ES6, Bootstrap 4, SaSS, LESS
- · Git. SVN
- MySQL, Google BigQyuery
- Core Java, Python.

TOOLS

- JIRA for Agile Project Management
- GITHUB for Software Development across teams
- Visual Studio, Atom, Eclipse for Web Development
- Tableau for Dashboards
- MYSQL for Database Administration
- Cloudera for Hadoop

EDUCATION

- Bachelors of Electronics Engineering DMCE - Univeristy of Mumbai (2009-2012)
- Diploma in Electronics Engineering MMJ Shah Polytechnic - MSBTE (2006-2009)

CERTIFICATIONS

 Backbase Frontend Developer Backbase Limited - Mar 18

ACHIEVEMENTS

- IEEE Judge for Software
 IEEE Hackathon Mumbai March 2019
- Outstanding Employee Lead Infosys Limited - March '18 & March '17

PROFILE

Backbase Certified Front End Developer with 6.8 years of technical experience in IT Industry in Web Development which is backed with a Bachelors of Engineering in Electronics. Hands on experience in frameworks like Backbase and Web Development tools such as Angular, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap4, JavaScript for effective deployment of website.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Consultant - Nexino Labs, Mumbai

Aug 2018 - January 2020

- Led a team of 18 for design and development of Company Portal using Angular and Node.
- Designed User Experience for Educational Courses website.
- Worked with the Backend team for creating multiple API's to be integrated with Front end.
- Created dashboards for CMS of specific pages of website.
- Integrated CRM with the website to get data from backend to be displayed for Consumers.
- Created reuseable components for effective use of code throughout the project using Angular.
- Followed agile Methodologies and managed Sprints for timely fulfillment of Website.
- Managed Scrum calls across teams for daily updates from the team.
- Approved delivery of Code after testing has been completed.
- Used Tableau to create dashboards in order to present meaningful insights to the client.

Technology Analyst - Infosys Technologies Ltd, Pune

Jun 2013 - Aug 2018

- Led a team of 12 for all project related activities in portal development using Backbase in financial domain.
- Developed widgets using component structure using Angular JS
 1.5 and Backbase 5.7 for a seamless experience.
- Understood and develop client requirements for a easy and effective user experience.
- Created multiple widgets as part of reusable component technique which can be used across by multiple teams.